theadultman.com 2019-01-26

# Privacy Policy & Disclaimer | The Adult Man

Below is the Privacy Policy & Disclaimer for use of TheAdultMan.com.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy or disclaimer, please feel free to contact me by email at dean@theadultman.com.

* * *

###  **privacy Policy**

* * *

Effective as of August 7th, 2018

As the owner of this website (the “Site”), **I, Dean Stephens  **(“me” or “I”) understand that your privacy is of critical importance.  This Privacy Policy describes what information I collect from you via the Site and how I use and disclose such information.

 **My Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that I store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

I use cookies for the following purposes:

(a) authentication – I use cookies to identify you when you visit my website and as you navigate my website;

(b) personalization – I use cookies [to store information about your preferences and to personalize the website for you];

(c) security – I use cookies as an element of the security measures used to protect user accounts, including preventing fraudulent use of login credentials, and to protect my website and services generally;

(d) advertising – I use cookies to help me to display advertisements that will be relevant to you; and

(e) analysis – I use cookies [to help us to analyze the use and performance of our website and services;

I use Google Analytics to analyze the use of my website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of my website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:

(a) <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en> (Chrome);

(b) <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences> (Firefox);

(c) [http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/](https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/) (Opera);

(d) <https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies>(Internet Explorer);

(e) <https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411> (Safari); and

(f) <https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy> (Edge).

Please note that blocking cookies may have a negative impact on the functions of many websites, including my Site. Some features of the Site may cease to be available to you.

 **Interest-Based Advertising**

Advertising Privacy Statement

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. I publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners.You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).  However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by me or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact me at dean@theadultman.com ** ** or contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners I work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

 **Email Addresses**

I may collect your email address, but only if you voluntarily provide it to me. This may occur, for example, if you sign up to receive an email newsletter, or enter a promotion. I will use your email address for the purposes for which you provided it to me, and also from time to time to send you emails regarding the Site or other products or services that I believe may be of interest to you. You may opt out of such email communications at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” button in the email.

I will not share your email address with any third parties.

If you are a resident of a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), please refer to the section below entitled “Additional Rights of EEA Residents.”

 **Registration or Account Data**

As you use the Site, I could collect other data that you provide voluntarily (such as comments that you post).

I may also collect information about you through other methods, including research surveys, social media platforms, verification services, data services, as well as public sources.

If you are a resident of a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), please refer to the section below entitled “Additional Rights of EEA Residents.”

 **Additional Rights of EEA (European Economic Area) Residents**

If you are a resident of a country in the EEA, you have the rights, among others, to:

(i)  access your personal data

(ii)  ensure the accuracy of your personal data

(iii) the right to have us delete your personal data

(iv)  the right to restrict further processing of your personal data, and

(v)  the right to complain to a supervisory authority in your country of residence in the event that data is misused

If you believe that my processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.

You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by notice to me addressed to dean@theadultman.com.

 **Sale of Business or Assets**

In the event that the Site or substantially all of its assets is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, the information I have collected about you may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction.

 **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

I may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Site, with the “Effective Date” posted at the top of the Policy. I may revise and update this Privacy Policy if my practices change, as technology changes, or as I add new services or change existing ones. If I make any material changes to my Privacy Policy or how I handle your personal information, or I are going to use any personal information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in my Privacy Policy at the time I collected such information, I will give you a reasonable opportunity to consent to the change. If you do not consent, your personal information will be used as agreed to under the terms of the privacy policy in effect at the time I  obtained that information. By using my Site or services after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to my then-current privacy policy. I will use information previously obtained in accordance with the Privacy Policy in effect when the information was obtained from you.

 **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of this Site, please contact me directly at  **dean@theadultman.com**

* * *

###  **TheAdultMan.com Disclaimer**

* * *

Effective as of August 7th, 2018.

TheAdultMan.com, this website, is for entertainment purposes only.  While we pride ourselves on providing accurate information, visitors use information on this site at their own risk. TheAdultMan.com will not compensate anyone in any way for losses or negative impacts suffered while making use of information found among the many posts, pages, and archives of TheAdultMan.com.

TheAdultMan.com reserves the right to make any modifications or corrections to the information you find on the website at any time without notice.

 **Comments and the responsibility of those leaving comments**

Writers of comments on this website will take full responsibility and liability for any libel or litigation that results from something written in or as a direct result of something written in a comment.  The accuracy, completeness, veracity, honesty, exactitude, factuality and politeness of comments are not guaranteed.  We do pride ourselves on keeping this civil and maintaining a friendly community.  By commenting on TheAdultMan.com, you grant TheAdultMan.com world-wide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, non-exclusive, fully sub-licensable license(s) to use, distribute, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, publicly perform and publicly display your comments (in whole or in part) and to incorporate your comments into other works in any format or medium now known or later developed.

 **Previously Published Posts**

Previously published posts and articles may from time to time be updated without notification.  Sometimes previously published posts and articles may contain out of date information or dead links.  Please see the “Last Updated” line at the top of each post.  It is the visitor’s/reader’s responsibility to obtain the most current data.
